亲爱的战友们
Fellow warriors,
我是征服者谢耳朵
This is sheldor the conqueror.
我们将要挺进阿克西多斯堡垒
We are about to enter axidus' fortress.
这是一场持久战  请大家做好排尿工作
Now, this is a long run, so let's do another bladder check.
好的  巴里  我们再等等你
All right, barry, we'll wait for you again,
不过我建议你最好去看医生了
But you really  should see a doctor.
谢耳朵暂时离开[网络用语]
Sheldor is afk.
佩妮  你好像有什么困难的样子
Penny, are you experiencing some sort of difficulty?
没错  我的门打不开了
Yes. I can't get  my stupid door open.
你有没有意识到你是正在
You appear to have put  your car key
用车钥匙开这扇门？
In the door lock-- are you aware of that?
是的
Yeah.
那好吧
All right, then.
妈的
Damn it,
妈的  妈的  妈的
Damn it, damn it, damn it, damn it!
你能尽量不出声吗
Would it be possible for you to do this a little more quietly?
这该死的钥匙拔不出来了
I can't get the damn key out.
那是肯定的  你那扇门上的鲍尔温锁
Well, it's not surprising-- that baldwin lock on your door
用的是传统的边缘齿
Uses traditional edge-mounted cylinders,
而你那辆大众的钥匙
Whereas the key for your volkswagen
用的是中间齿系统
Uses a center cylinder system.
谢谢你  谢尔顿
Thank you, sheldon.
别客气
You're welcome.
那你到底干嘛
Why did you put
要把汽车钥匙塞到门锁里去
Your car key in the door lock?
想知道为什么吗  我来告诉你  今天我有一次试镜
Why? I'll tell you why-- because today I had an audition,
我跑到那儿去花了两小时
It took me two hours  to get there,
然后又等了一小时才轮到我
I waited an hour for my turn,
而在我开始之前
And before I could even start,
他们却告诉我
They told me  I looked too midwest
我长得太中西部化了
For the part.
太中西部化  这他妈的算什么意思
Too midwest-- what the hell  does that even mean?
在美国中西部定居的人们
Well, the american midwest was mostly settled
大多都是斯堪的纳维亚和日耳曼血统的
By scandinavian and germanic people.
他们脸部的毛发结构是很有特色的
They have a characteristic facial bone structure...
我知道这是什么意思  谢尔顿
I know what it means, sheldon!
上帝啊  我来洛杉矶已经快两年了
God! you know, I have been in l.a. for almost two years now,
还没演过一出戏
And I haven't gotten  a single acting job.
我什么事业都没完成
I've accomplished nothing, haven't gotten
工资也没涨  而且有六个月没做爱了
A raise at work, haven't   even had sex in six months,
就刚才  我在上楼梯的时候
And just now, when I was    walking up those stairs,
一只苍蝇飞进我嘴巴里  我居然把它吃下去了
A fly flew in my mouth  and I ate it!
实际上昆虫是很多国家餐桌上的必备
Well, actually, insects are a dietary staple in many cultures.
差不多就可以把它们看作蛋白质
They're almost pure protein.
我草你娘的
Oh, son of a bitch!
我认为是的那些冷冻食物的融化
I believe the condensation on your frozen foods
削弱了你纸袋的强度
Weakened the structural integrity of the bag.
我们还是回到你那钥匙的问题上吧
But returning to your key conundrum,
你应该去叫一个锁匠
Perhaps you should call a locksmith
-来帮你开门  -我叫过了
And have him  open the door for you. I did.
他说他什么时候到就什么时候到
He said he'll get here   when he gets here.
你是不是因为他给你重复而无意义的回答
And you're frustrated  because he phrased his reply
-而变得如此癫狂  -没有
In the form of a meaningless tautology? no!
我之所以这样是因为我的人生充满了失败
I am frustrated because I am a failure at everything
还有我嘴巴里有苍蝇味道
And my breath smells like fly.
不哭
There, there.
你想到我们的屋子里等吗
Would you prefer to wait in our apartment?
不  谢尔顿  我想坐在这冰冷的地板上
No, sheldon, I'd rather sit on this freezing-cold floor
像三岁小孩一样哭
Sobbing like a three-year-old.
那好吧
All right, then.
看在上帝的份上
For heaven's sake.
我还当我掌握到挖苦的窍门了呢
Just when I think I've gotten the hang of sarcasm.
《生活大爆炸》
第二季  第03集
你随便坐
Make yourself comfortable.
那里不行
Not there.
谢耳朵回来了
Sheldor is back online.
谢耳朵?
Sheldor?
征服者
The conqueror.
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
暂时离开
Afk.
我在玩科南时代  一个背景是
I'm playing age of conan,   an online multiplayer game
罗伯特·E·霍华德科南野蛮时代的网络游戏
Set in the universe of robert e. howard's conan the barbarian.
谢耳朵回来了
Sheldor back online.
什么是"afk"
What's "afk"?
Afk
Afk.
暂时离开一下键盘
Away from keyboard.
知晓了
Oh, I see.
你那是代表什么意思
What does that stand for?
知晓了
Oh, I see.
我听见了  但那是代表什么
Yes, but what does it stand for?
点击那只魔化的靴子  就能穿上了
Now, just click on the enchanted boots to put them on.
等等啊  我能换一种颜色吗
Mm, I don't know-- can I see them in another color?
点它就是了
Just click on them.
祝贺你 你现在是一个3级的战士了
Yeah, congratulations. You are now a level-three warrior.
-怎么回事  -莱纳德
What's going on? leonard,  guess what?
我是一个3级战士了
I'm a level-three warrior.
很好
Great.
你知道你门外东西掉了一地么
Do you know there are groceries outside of your apartment?
知道知道知道
Yeah, yeah, yeah. shh.
我只是想告诉你  你的冰淇淋已经融化了
I only bring it up because your ice cream's melting
而且招来了野生动物
And it's starting to attract wildlife.
知道了
Uh-huh, yeah.
我现在应该守在丛林里还是去海滩
Do I stay in the jungle or go towards the beach?
无所谓  你现在的任务是找财宝
It doesn't matter-- right now; you're looking for treasure.
等等  你去哪儿
Wait, wait, where are you going?
不  不  没事
No, no. you're okay.
如果你碰到鳄鱼  就用靴子踢它
If you run into crocodiles, just kick them with your boots.
你能告诉我怎么了吗
You want to catch me up?
好吧
Well, let's see, uh,
她尝试用车钥匙来开门
She attempted to open her apartment with her car key
因为她的脸太中西部化了
Because her face is overly midwestern, um...
她六个月没做爱了
She hasn't had sex in six months...
还有她吃了一只苍蝇
And she ate a fly.
真的吗  六个月
Seriously?  six months?
天呐
Oh, my god!
一个财宝箱  我发财了
A treasure chest! I'm rich!
才3级就觉得自己发财了
Level three, and she thinks she's rich.
真是个新手
What a newb.
好了
Okay...
万事俱备
We're all set.
开始吧
Let her rip.
嗨
Hi.
快看  这只是玉米淀粉和水
Check it out-- it's just   corn starch and water.
它们组成
They make up
非牛顿流体  也就是液体
A non-newtonian fluid, which is liquid,
但是在音箱的冲击作用下呈现固态
But solid under the percussive action of the speaker.
知道它的魅力所在了吧
That's what makes it get all funky.
好吧
Yeah. okay.
听着  我要和谢尔顿说两句
Uh, listen, I need to talk to sheldon.
没有  她说的就是谢尔顿
No, that's what she said-- sheldon.
我在游戏里
Okay, I'm in the game,
我正在托泰吉岛探险
And I've been exploring the island of tortage,
但我不知道怎么通过船长护卫
But I can't figure out how to get past the guard captain.
你有魔剑么
Do you have the enchanted sword?
没有  我有个铜匕首
No, no, I have a bronze dagger.
你用铜匕首是打不过船长护卫的
You can't slay the guard captain with a bronze dagger.
天呐  这跟你用车钥匙
My lord, it's like the car key
开公寓的门一个道理
In your apartment door all over again.
好吧  我怎么能得到那把剑
All right, how do I get the sword?
你有没有去过米希拉神庙
Well, have you been to the temple of mishra?
你是说山上那个
Is that the place on the hill with
-门前站着好多诡异的牧师  -不对不对
-The weird priest in front of it? -no, no, no, it's...
我的老天  还是给我吧
Oh, for god's sakes, gimme.
谢谢  感激不尽
Thank you-- I really appreciate this.
你必须学会
You're gonna have to learn
自己做这些事  佩妮
To do these things for yourself, penny.
别管我了  赶快给我把剑搞来
Don't patronize me-- just get the sword!
有没有搞错
What the frack?
我真晕
Beats me.
他们昨天玩了一晚上
They were playing all last night, too.
就像那种把两个不相干的人物扯到一起的恶搞动漫
It's like some kind of weird comic book crossover.
就像绿巨人和薄荷佩蒂约会
Like if hulk were dating peppermint patty.
我一直以为薄荷佩蒂是蕾丝边呢
I always thought peppermint patty was a lesbian.
不  那是玛茜
No, that's marcie.
薄荷佩蒂只是比较运动型
Peppermint patty's just athletic.
好了  魔剑到手
There you go-- one enchanted sword.
好的  给我给我
All right, gimme, gimme, gimme.
看我把那个船长守卫杀了的
I want to kill the guard captain.
那个女孩真应该好好过日子
That girl needs to get a life.
谢尔顿
Sheldon?
Sheldon...
危险警报
Danger! danger!
没事  是我佩妮
No danger--  it's just me, penny.
听着  我现在25级了
Listen, I got to level 25
然后到了紫莲花沼泽对吧
And reached purple lotus swamp, right?
你在我的卧室里
You're in my bedroom.
莱纳德给了我应急钥匙
Leonard gave me an emergency key.
我的卧室不许外人进的
People can't be in my bedroom.
那我们去客厅说吧
Well, can we go talk in the living room?
但我没有穿睡裤
I'm not wearing pajama bottoms.
为什么
Why not?
我把葡萄汁洒上了
I spilled grape juice.
那就穿别的睡裤啊
Well, wear different pajamas.
我不能穿别的睡裤  这是我周一的睡裤
I can't wear different pajamas--  these are my monday pajamas.
佩妮  我的卧室不许外人进的
Penny, people cannot be in my bedroom.
好吧  你就告诉我  现在就去 黑色城堡探险是不是早了点
Okay, fine, just tell me, is it too soon to join a quest to the black castle?
-有人邀请你去黑色城堡探险么  -没错
-You were invited on a quest to the black castle? -yeah, yeah.
布达佩斯的几个人找我去的
By some guys in budapest.
我就是不太确定我的人物该不该去
I'm just not sure it's the right move for my character.
当然不该  你才 25级
Of course it's not--   you're only a level 25.
这些匈牙利人 他们把你当龙的诱饵
These hungarians, they're just using you for dragon fodder.
真的么  我怎么就信了 那群匈牙利蛮夷的呢
Really? boy, you'd think you could trust a horde of hungarian barbarians.
拜托  佩妮  够了 我得睡觉了
Please, penny, enough. I have to sleep.
好吧  你真强 谢谢
Okay, well, you were great. Thanks.
莱纳德  不要进谢尔顿的房间 他没穿睡裤
Oh. hey, leonard. listen,  don't go in sheldon's room he's not wearing bottoms.
谢尔顿  你愿意再提示我一下么
Sheldon, you want  to catch me up again?
我今天很忙
People, I am very busy today.
我知道  盖博豪斯博士
I realize that, dr. gablehauser,
但作为系主任
But it is your job, as  head of the department,
协调不同院系的矛盾是你的工作
To mediate all interdepartmental disputes.
学校工作手册 第四章  第二节
University policy manual, chapter Four, Subsection Two:
"协调院系间的矛盾"
"mediation of interdepartmental disputes."
好吧
Fine.
温克尔博士
Dr. winkle, what colorful name
这次你又给库珀博士取什么外号了
Did you call dr. cooper this time?
傻蛋博士
Dr. dumb-ass.
库珀博士  温克尔博士道歉了
Dr. cooper, dr. winkle apologizes.
-不  我没有  -不  她没有
No, I don't. no, she doesn't.
问题是这样
Here's the problem.
我很明确地做了登记
I was clearly signed up
来使用博克曼实验室204室的主机
To use the mainframe in buckman 204,
而温克尔博士却粗暴地
And dr. winkle just wantonly
把它们都撕了下来
Ripped the sign-up sheet off the wall.
那甚至都不是正式的登记表格
It wasn't even an official sign-up sheet.
他自己打印出来
He printed it himself, and he put his name down
在每一个机位都写上自己的名字  使用六个月
On every slot for the next six months.
如果保证学校的资源 不被浪费在
If it is a crime to ensure that the university's resources
追逐亚原子界的野鹅敢死队  是有罪的话
Are not being squandered chasing subatomic wild geese,
那么我承认我错了
Then I plead guilty.
-佩妮! -你要接那个电话么  库珀博士
-Oh, penny! -do you need To get that, dr. cooper?
-才不  -别关机啊
-God, no. -Well, don't turn it off,
你可能会错过诺贝尔委员会
You might miss your call from the nobel committee
提名你为年度荣誉傻蛋
Letting you know you've been nominated
的通知
As dumb-ass laureate of the year.
是么
Oh, yeah? well...
那你连提名都不会被提名
You wouldn't even be nominated.
盖博豪斯博士  我需要运行
Dr. gablehauser,  I have a series
一系列重要的模拟和计算
Of important calculations  and simulations to run.
而她只是简化一些毫无关系的数据
All she's doing is reducing irrelevant data
然后嘲笑
And making a mock...
抱歉
Excuse me.
盖博豪斯
Gablehauser.
打给你的
It's for you.
喂
Hello?
佩妮  现在不方便说话
Penny, this is not a good time.
不  我跟你说过 你还不能去焚灵圣殿
No, I told you, you're not prepared for the sanctum of burning souls.
你得组个至少5人的队去
You need to be in a group of at least five for that quest
1个35级的医师
And one should be a level 35 healer.
佩妮  我不能上线帮你
Penny, I can't log on and help you.
等我回家再说
We'll talk when I get home.
我没沉迷网游  对吧
I'm not getting the computing time, am i?
傻蛋
Dumb-ass.
莱纳德  你得想办法解决佩妮
Leonard, you have to do something about penny.
她妨碍我睡觉
She is interfering with my sleep,
她妨碍我工作
She's interfering with my work,
我生活中要是还有其他重要面
And if I had another significant aspect of my life,
我肯定她也会参一脚
I'm sure she'd be interfering with that, too.
为什么要我想办法
Why should I do something?
-是你教她网游的  -没错
You're the one who introduced  her to online gaming. yes,
但她刚搬来时  是你去招惹她的
But you're the one who said hello to her when she moved in.
要是你当时克制自己
If you'd simply restrained yourself,
就不会发生这些事了
None of this would be happening.
干嘛不直接跟她说别烦你
Why don't you just tell her to leave you alone?
我跟她说了
I did, I told her,
我发信息给她  我发了个斩钉截铁的Twitter邮件[即时信息]
I texted her, I sent out a very emphatic twitter.
就连我的Facebook状态都改成
I even changed my facebook status to
希望佩妮勿扰的谢尔顿·库珀
"sheldon cooper wishes penny would leave him alone."
我不知道还能怎么办
I don't know what else to do.
那我又能做什么
Well, what am I supposed to do?
我不知道  但如果你不想点主意
I don't know, but if you don't figure something out,
我警告你  我会变得相当难相处
I warn you, I shall become very difficult to live with.
你是说直到现在  我们都体验着
You mean up until now we've been experiencing
快乐  祥和的谢尔顿
The happy, fun-time Sheldon?
-没错  -我这就跟她谈
Yes. I'll go talk to her.
不  德国佬  我要你帮我防侧面
No, fritz, I need you on my flank.
不  我不会说德语
No, I don't know german.
侧面  侧面[伪德语]
Flankenzei, flankenzei.
-佩妮  -忙呢
Hey, Penny.Busy.
我看到了
Yeah, I see that.
你不是要上班吗
Shouldn't you be at work?
我周一不上班
I don't work on mondays.
今天是周四
It's thursday.
这样的  佩妮
Listen, Penny...
珀涅罗珀女王[奥德赛的妻子]  暂时离开
Queen penelope, afk.
干嘛
What...?
是这样的
Here's the thing.
有时候  有些人  好人
Sometimes people, good people,
他们开始玩网游
Yeah, they start playing these games
然后发现自己
And they find themselves--
非自己过失  不知不觉地
Through no fault of their own--
有点  上瘾了
You know, kind of...addicted.
明白  我快升级了
Yeah, get to the point.I'm about to level up here.
只是如果一个人
It's just if a person doesn't have
在现实生活中缺乏成就感
A sense of achievement in their real life,
就很容易在虚拟世界迷失自我
It's easy to lose themselves in a virtual world
他们在那只能得到假的成就感
Where they can get a false sense of accomplishment.
对  唏哩哗啦  好了  小子们
Yeah, jabber, jabber, jabber.okay, boys,
珀涅罗珀女王归队了
Queen penelope's back online.
佩妮  你
Penny, you've got...
头发上有奇多[一种零食]
Cheetos in your hair.
谢谢
Oh. thanks.
佩妮  又是我  莱纳德
Hey, Penny, it's me again, Leonard.
莱纳德  我说了没时间
Leonard, I said not now.
我知道  我只是有点担心你
I know, I'm just a little concerned about you.
我说了没时间
I said not now!
好吧  以后说吧
Okay, maybe later.
伙计们
Hey, guys.
他怎么了
Hey, what's with him?
佩妮晚上一直烦他
Penny's been keeping him up at night.
我也是
Me, too.
但用另一种方式
But probably in a different way.
她迷上柯南时代
She's gotten really hooked on age of conan.
一直在玩  没停过
She's playing nonstop.
对  沉溺网游
Ah, yes, online gaming addiction.
没什么比
There's nothing worse than having
被多玩家高手追在后面更糟的
That multi-player monkey on your back.
谢尔顿  醒醒
Sheldon, wake up!
危险  危险
Danger! danger!
中午好  男士们
Afternoon, men.
谢尔顿
Sheldon.
行啊
Oh, yeah?
你想通过把我从成人男性里排除
Well, your attempt at juvenilizing me
抑制我成长  只是
By excluding me from the set of adult males, just...
我累得吵不出来了
Oh, I'm too tired to do this.
对  我听说你通宵和 中土大陆娃娃夜战
Right.I heard you've been pulling all-nighters with middle earth barbie.
她跑到我房间里
She comes into my room.
没人能随便进我房间
No one's supposed to be in my room.
我觉得她只是逃到网络世界
I would postulate that she's escaping into the online world
以弥补她的性挫折
To compensate for her sexual frustration.
我也是这样
I do that, too.
但用另一种方式
But probably in a different way.
不是这样的  莱斯利
That's not what she's doing, Leslie.
她只是想拾回她的自尊心
She's just trying to shore up her self-esteem.
跟性没关系
It has nothing to do with sex.
任何事物都和性有关
Everything has to do with sex.
正确
Mm, testify.
我不会碰它的
I'm not touching that.
莱斯利  你扯太远了
Leslie, you are way off base here.
等等  莱纳德 虽然我藐视莱斯利的科学家身份
Hang on, leonard. While I have no respect for Leslie as a scientist
或者做人这点
Or a human being,for that matter,
我们必须 承认她在滥交和随便的性爱领域中
We have to concede her undeniable expertise in the interrelated fields
不可否认的经验
Of promiscuity and general sluttiness.
谢谢
Thank you.
我是说那个小叮当[小飞侠里面的小精灵]只是需要一点慰藉
My point is that tinker bell just needs to get her some.
一些什么 哦  知道了  一些性事
Some what? Oh, yes, some sexual intercourse.
我主动献身
I'll take the bullet.
不好意思  这主意太馊了
Excuse me, this whole idea is insane.
别争了  我准备采取行动了
Enough debate, I'm going to take action.
打扰一下
Excuse me.
你目前有固定性关系吗
Are you currently involved in a sexual relationship?
没有
No.
你想有吗
Would you like to be?
当然  何乐不为
Uh... sure, why not?
谢尔顿
Sheldon...
别  别  别
Puh-puh-puh.
能要你的电话号码吗
Can I have your phone number?
好的
Uh... yeah.
看  问题解决了
There. problem solved.
傻蛋
Dumb-ass.
我在古城瑰宝的大门外 我要进去了
Okay, I'm at the gate to the treasury of the ancients. I'm going in.
-紧挨着墙走 躲开木乃伊  -明白
-Stay close to the wall. Avoid the mummies. -got it.
不得不说你仅23岁  就是个高手女性玩家
I must say you're playing very well for a woman of 23.
-22岁 好的  -22岁
-Twenty-two. -Right, 22.
[网络征友信息]
木乃伊过来了 我该用哪招  夺命拳 还是定身咒
Oh, here come the mummies. Which spell do I use, the hateful strike or the frenzy stance?
你团队中的其他人呢
What happened to the rest of your group?
我把他们甩了  他们是一帮衰人
I dumped them, they're a bunch of wussies.
定身咒
Frenzy stance.
定住  定住  定住  定住  定住
Frenzy, frenzy, frenzy, frenzy, frenzy.
你能描述下你理想中的假期吗
So, listen, would you describe your ideal vacation
在不知名的小岛上野外探险 还是窝在家里捧本好书
As a wild adventure to unknown lands or staying at home curled up with a good book?
什么
What?
这些是市场调查问题
These are market research questions.
我在为你的游戏做在线注册
I'm filling out the online registration for your game.
好的  野外探险
Oh, okay, wild adventure.
定身咒不管用
Oh, frenzy stance isn't working.
死  你这不死的木乃伊  死
Die, you undead mummy, die!
服一剂疗伤药 -谢谢  -不客气
Drink a healing potion. Thank you. you're welcome.
从1到5五个等级 1是完全他主动
Anyhow, on a scale of one to five, with one being always initiated by him
5是完全你主动  你的性爱级别是几
And five being always initiated by you, how do you prefer your sexual encounters to begin?
注册需要写这个吗
That's on the registration?
是的  非常深入的调查
Oh, yes, it's quite extensive.
不过如果填完 你可以得到免费的升级包
But if we complete it, you get a free expansion pack.
外加75个新增的任务
75 additional quests.
太棒了  我绝对喜欢主动  我铁定是5级
Ooh, awesome, okay, I totally like to initiate. I'm a big ol' five.
知道了
Good to know.
铁定的5级
Big ol' five.
你好
Hello.
嗨
Hi.
莱纳德  这是汤姆
Leonard, this is tom.
嗨  汤姆  谢尔顿
Hi, tom.   sheldon...
难道我没告诉你 在自助餐厅里的小误会吗
Didn't I explain to you about your little mistake in the cafeteria?
说了 如饭桌上别的人一样 你表述得非常清楚
Yes, you were very clear. As was everyone else at the table.
不过汤姆是经过科学筛选出来
Tom, however, has been chosen by science
的适合佩妮的约会对象
As a suitable mate for penny.
科学筛选
Chosen by science?
通过交友网站的科学系统
Well, what passes for science on dating sites.
声称用了启发式算法 但估计是胡说八道
They claim to use heuristic algorithms, but it may well be hokum.
你让佩妮登记去网上交友
You got penny to sign up for online dating?
不是  当然不是 我欺骗使诈来着
No, of course not. See, I used trickery and deceit.
这下糟糕了
This is bad.
汤姆是消防队的护工
Tom is a paramedic with the fire department,
但他晚上去医学院上课
But he's going to med school at night.
他喜欢户外活动
He likes the outdoors
喜欢强悍在性上主动的女人
And, uh, strong women who initiate sex.
太  太糟了
Really, really bad.
我很奇怪你在佩妮那儿都没有上垒
I'm surprised you struck out with penny.
她可是超级5级型
Apparently, she's a big ol' five.
谢尔顿  你想干嘛
Sheldon, what do you want?
哦  不错 你收到我留言了 佩妮  我想让你见见汤姆
Oh, good, you got my note. Penny, I'd like you to meet tom.
佩妮  这是汤姆 汤姆  容我介绍佩妮
Penny, this is tom. Tom, may I present penny.
嗨  佩妮
Hi, penny.
恩  嗨  听着 只要我一上线
Yeah, hey. listen... As long as I'm here,
就被一群菜鸟包围着问问题 这些人根本找不着北
I'm on a quest with a bunch of newbs. They don't know what they're doing.
我们有一个刺客 三个使咒者  无战车
We've got one assassin, three spell casters and no tank.
-这个我们能玩点再谈吗 -不行 不行  我现在就需要你
-Can we talk about this later? -No, no, no, no. I need you now.
你难道不想和汤姆交往一下吗
Wouldn't you prefer to socialize with tom,
他是个性上被动  喜欢户外的人
Who is a sexually passive outdoorsman?
随便了  我自己想办法
Whatever. I'll figure it out myself.
再见  佩妮
Bye, penny.
不好意思  伙计  她和照片上简直是两个人
I'm sorry, dude, she didn't look anything like her picture.
从来都是这样的
They never do
你好  美女佩妮
hello, fair penny.
你是谁
Who are you?
是我  霍华德·沃罗威茨先生
It is i, sir howard of wolowitz.
能邀请你去那边的虚拟酒馆喝上壶麦芽酒
Can I interest you in an afternoon of spirited questing
在精神世界中畅游消磨下午时光吗
Followed by a flagon of ale at yon virtual tavern?
好的  当然  干嘛不呢
Yeah, sure, why not?
天哪  救救我吧
Oh, my god, I need help.